Wow, this book is the best!
[CONSTRUCTION NOISES]
Okay, what are those sounds?
Match! Do you know what those sounds are?
What sounds?
[SHATTER]
Oh, that?
Yeah. Come on, Match, let's find out!
Awhhh...
Hey! That's the ICRC!
What?
Uh, you know, the Ice Cube Recovery Center?
The place where Ice Cube is created when she dies?
Wow, coolio.
What's going on?
Come take a look.
Cool! It's Ice Cube, and she's shrinking!
No, she's falling.
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
Hey, Snowball.
Remember how that Weird Speaker Box told
us our team would be getting a new player?
Yeah, of COURSE I remember!
COINY:
I wonder who it'll be?
Well, Coiny, you're about to find out.
Oh, and don't call me a Weird Speaker Box.
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da ♪
♪ Cake at Stake! ♪
So, the votes are in, and I've gathered
the six eliminated players here today.
One of you will be joining the Squashy Grapes,
who are impatiently waiting over there.
The person rejoining the game gets
both this cake and this Win Token.
Hey, that's not fair!
They do worse than us by getting
eliminated, and still, they get a Win Token?!
Ha-ha! Stinks for you not to have a Win Token yet!
So, there was a total of twenty-eight votes.
Luckily for all of you, you
all got at least one vote.
- Woody...
- Ehhh?
I'm sorry to tell you this, but you only got one vote.
You go back to the Tiny Loser Chamber.
WOODY:
EEEEEEEEHHHH!!
The TLC seems LARGER!
I enlarged it.
With four votes each, there is a
three-way tie for third place.
Pin, you're one of the members of the tie.
You won't rejoin the game.
What? That's CRAZY!
AAAAHHHH!
ANNOUNCER:
Spongy-Spongy, you too.
SPONGY:
UUUUUHHHHH!
Also losing is...
If you re-eliminate me,
I'll crush you with my recently-refurbished
ANNOUNCER CRUSHER!!!
Well, too bad for me. You're out.
GRRRRRR!!
WAAAAAAOOOOUUAAAAH!
NO!
So, it's down to Needy-
DON'T call me Needy!
-and Blocky.
The Stabber and the Stabbable.
Don't call me STABBABLE!
Now, rejoining the game
on the Squashy Grapes team is...
...Blocky the Stabbable.
YEAH! But seriously, don't call me Stabbable.
Needle, with a measly seven votes, you lose.
Aw, seri-
Yeah! A new team, guys!
Contestants, we have reached a new
stage in the Battle For Dream Island.
You are the final fifteen.
As a reward, you all get BFDI posters.
GRR! I was hoping for a BETTER reward!
Okay, stash those away, because we gotta move on.
Squishy Cherries, do you notice that you are
exactly half the size of the Squashy Grapes team?
Oh, ha-ha. You know, you don't have to rub it OIN!
Well, that means the Grape team will permanently
be permanently split permanently in two,
permanently forming three
teams of five, permanently.
Oh, my mint, are you W-ing serious?!
I liked being on the LARGER team.
Hyuk-hyuk-doy, you better believe I'm serious.
Leafy and Rocky will choose the teams.
Why them?! Why not ME?!
Well, for one, they don't have archenemies.
Plus, their names are five letters long.
I like the number five.
So Leafy, choose first.
LEAFY:
Ah-ha! Ice Cube, come on down! You can be my ally!
Thanks for picking me!
Pencil wouldn't let me into her alliance.
That was almost a year ago, Icy.
Let it go!
Rocky, your turn.
Rocky?
Come on, Rocky, Speak up!
Don't you know? Rocky forgot
how to talk in episode four.
So how does he communicate?
ROCKY:
Bleh!
He picks TB.
Teardrop, 'kay?
Wha?
Teardrop! Should she join or not?
She's got to join!
We'll pick Golf Ball because she and I are a DUO!
Okay...
Out of the people left, Snowball seems the best.
I'm the BEST out of ALL people!
Coiny, Firey, or Blocky?
Coiny!
Hmm...
Blocky or Firey? Blocky or Firey?
I'd say Blocky. I'm better friends with him!
Wait! But then Firey goes to my team,
and he's just so dumb!
I know you are, but what am I?
See? You're so dumb, you don't even know what you are!
Name-choosing time.
Leafy, Icy, TD, SB, and Blocky, choose your name.
You know, I've been a Squashy Grape for so long,
I think we should continue
to be the Squashy Grapes!
Sounds good?
Uh...yeah!
Then that's your team name.
Okay, moving on.
Rocky, TB, GB, Coiny, and Firey, what's your name?
Ooh, ooh! I wanna be the Squashy Grapes, too!
No, NO!
The others are already the Squashy Grapes!
Our name has to be ANOTHER NAME!
So then your team is Another Name.
Wait, I-
Let's go through our current teams.
Squishy Cherries,
Squashy Grapes,
and Another Name.
Um, Awkward Speaker Cube?
Last episode, you said TWO
people would be eliminated.
What's that about?
Well, during the voting period, voters
will vote two people off the losing team.
Afterward, the winning team chooses
one of the two onto their team.
Nothing happens to the middle team.
Okay, sounds good, unusual talking rectangle!
Okay, enough talking. Let's get to it.
The ninth-
Which IIIS?!
The ninth contest is a six-legged race.
Here are ropes to tie your legs together.
Go!
Come on, Grapes! TIE UP!
LOOK! The Mushy Berries are already going!
Ow! Aughuah! Ow! Agh! Ow! Aoouugh! Oo!
Ouughuuaagh! Blaah! BLAAH! BLAAAAAAH!
BLAAAAAEEEEEGH!
GRR!
AH!
You SLOWPOKES are taking. TOO. LONG!
Seriously, SB, CALM DOWN!
Can't you at least help?
Oh, I'll help alright!
Now you're all tied up. No need to thank!
Wow, we're winning! That doesn't happen a lot!
Yeah, sure, Bubble.
Uh, guys, make sure to avoid that tree.
Ooh! Egh! Augh! Ack! Ooo! Eugh! Ow!
OOF!
Ooh! Ow! Egh! Ack! Ooo! Augh! Eugh!
Aren't races like this great?
Yeah!
And if we could walk IN SYNCHRONY,
IT WOULD BE EVEN BETTER!!!
Bleh!
Hey! It slimed me!
Euuugh...
HNNNGH...
UUUGH!
Hnnngh!
Wouldn't it be easier to-
Shu-SHUT IT!
HNNNNNNGH!
HNNNNNNNGH!
Ughhh...
Hheeeehhhh...
This-this is amazing! I mean, for so long,
Uh-we-we've been in last place,
and I-uh-I imagine that
when we are finally in first
place, it'll be so magical!
If we're quiet, they won't notice we're ahead.
WE'RE AHEAD?!
- Quiet, you!
- Well, YOU'RE not so quiet!
GASP!
It's a TIGHTROPE!
Ehh, I-I have a fear of heights...
- AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
- Huh? Ah! The Names are ahead!
- We have to catch up!
- AAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!
They've spotted us! Go, GO!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up, HURRY UP, HURRY UP!!!
The finish! It's right there!
Bleh!
WHOOOAAA!
OOF!
YOY!
Yay. Squishy Cherries, you're team number winner.
You'll be expecting a new player next episode.
Team Another Name, you're team number middle.
You don't win or lose.
But that means Ice Cube's team,
the Squashy Grapes, falls into last place.
They are the losers.
So voters, choose just one of
the following people to vote off:
Ice Cube, or those other four.
The two most voted people will leave the Squashy Grapes.
One will be chosen into the Squishy Cherries.
Hnnngh...
Hnnnnngh...
So tired...
Heeeeuuuuuugh...
Huuuuughhhhh...
You know, when you fall into a
bottomless pit, you die of starvation.